{
    "subject": "resource/Neo-Assyrian_Empire",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Nineveh",
    "human_readable": "The capital of the Neo-Assyrian Empire is Nineveh.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8935208916664124,
            "question": "What was the capital of the Neo-Assyrian Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8820757865905762,
            "question": "Which empire had Nineveh as its capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8187676668167114,
            "question": "What role did Nineveh play in the Neo-Assyrian Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6688022017478943,
            "question": "Is Nineveh considered a historical city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.554636538028717,
            "question": "Where was Nineveh located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4252737760543823,
            "question": "What is known about the culture of the Neo-Assyrian Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35934069752693176,
            "question": "Were there any significant architectural or artistic achievements during the Neo-Assyrian Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3029648959636688,
            "question": "When did the Neo-Assyrian Empire flourish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24279151856899261,
            "question": "How powerful was the Neo-Assyrian Empire at its peak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2350601851940155,
            "question": "What ultimately led to the decline of the Neo-Assyrian Empire?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of the Neo-Assyrian Empire is Nineveh.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9089_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How powerful was the Neo-Assyrian Empire at its peak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9089_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the Neo-Assyrian Empire flourish?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9089_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant architectural or artistic achievements during the Neo-Assyrian Empire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9089_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9089_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information that supports the statement. Nineveh was indeed the ancient capital city of the Neo-Assyrian Mesopotamian Empire, and it was located on the eastern bank of the Tigris River, which is in what is today northern Iraq."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents support that Nineveh was the capital of the Neo-Assyrian Empire. Multiple sources indicate that Nineveh was a significant and central city in the Neo-Assyrian Empire, including being its largest and most powerful city at certain points in time."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}